Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal is
so good that you agree one mango ginger
notice finally on time there is sub inspector
number 1500 son of Reena Golan 10 questions
they while speaking in it's ok ok
ok during the traffic and one should always
indicate change and
yes listen basically in this question and
basically in this question a skin the id 2nd
[music]
id to the answer ok ok ok during
subscribe and one should always indicate and
[music]
suddenly increase your speed on the highway suddenly
increase your speed on the highway
that you should suddenly change your speed is it right
or wrong okay if there is anyone behind you or
still it is okay to do this if if if it is
data if it is morning time or back it
is okay if because the traffic is less it is
not okay and someone should do this and everyone should
always do it and give indicator
subscribe like this a
pot in this day  And Arduino with rally
reaching reaching at last question solve so let's
tomorrow will be doing last point
question solve don't miss this chance and till then
answer this question only 1995 thank you all those who have
not participated in the question yet they should also do so
and become a part of us and
make these roads of ours because we
all
use routes but still the route is not saved
and hence to make them we have to
start with small tips and the last
tip is not everything happens
one to one and if anything is the
first step to start any new beginning then it is
Avyansh and from this small
question we are getting a lot of awareness that
if suddenly there is a
change in the wires painting question in the highway then
we can learn some things related to some rules and rules should
always be followed for our
like if we see that if we
talk about this question which you are now  We are
discussing this, it becomes clear from this
if we
suddenly change our speed on any side by increasing the speed
and this option is also different
that if it is only then why is it only,
if it is not only only then why is it not saved, so not only this,
you can also see the situation then you
can question change highway ok no option behind ok ok
during playlist
traffic and did not no one should always give in
Hindi also if you are on
a highway,
suddenly changing the speed while increasing your speed, have you
learned to change the speed or not, if we
are on a highway and we are increasing our speed and
suddenly changing the speed while increasing the speed very quickly
options ok then it is absolutely fine if there is
no one behind you ok status it is okay to do so
if time is right or again it is okay
during because it is not right to do
that everyone and
everyone should always change the plane by turning on the lights
and should indicate in advance question and
answer the questions end  The
answer in this question is the question is a
question that we have a lot of so the first thing is that
we have to go away
and we get to know
how our video should be and the second is that
because we are getting to know that our lion
here and what to do on the road is
dangerous, so we slowly
start changing ourselves, leaving aside the last things, we start doing
things, everyone
starts doing it with the entire team and will definitely
Ajay Devgan
change himself, so definitely the country and all the road
to the question, by doing this in such a way that
all our benefits are there, we are a part
of this campaign, you all are becoming a part of this campaign, through this
you are changing your behavior
and are just making roots,
saving the lives of those people, this
saving life is paste and roots and give so many
benefits, that is why we did it
and we have become a part of it,
we have started making road tiffin
about trees.  And to spread awareness, to
tell your friends and family about it and involve them in it and
invite them also so that they
too become a part of us, started a fast,
some people rules and every day
marriage, Wind Pipe questions and today
plastic packing dip tomorrow will last it is in
just three and family about, there is
not much time to tell them this question, question question, question question, question will be coming
tomorrow in August, we will answer it,
so start that every day after taking question, tomorrow will take only in this is
not the question, Aryan
teacher to our sewing, fright night fall
club after 200th test question, question question
to answer the question is possible
traffic rules, road safety rules for our own
loot-loot the small-small,
by subscribing we
will not only quote but also more  The producers will be the same
and Saif Ali will be there and who
knows, seeing you, other road users might
change their behaviour so this vision or action will motivate
people will notice people about this is the
current situation of road from chronic
fruit fruit question okay okay okay during the
traffic or not and one should always be quote ling
change stupid hand suit things that you are in this
situation will do if you
and you daily if you had to take the decision that
if you daily use painting while doing it
[music]
subscribe and exciting prices road
to truth about the road to reduce the number
of everyday is
one of